Guide to the Richard Marshall Collection of Gay Erotica and Pornography MSS.498
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III. Zines, 1964-2009, undated; 2 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons.
  - Straight to Hell: "The Manhattan Review of Unnatural Acts". Ed. Billy Miller. New York. 1979. n.43 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Straight to Hell: "The Manhattan Review of Unnatural Acts". Ed. Billy Miller. New York. n.44, Undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Straight to Hell: "The Manhattan Review of Unnatural Acts". Ed. Billy Miller. New York. n.45, Undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Straight to Hell: "The Manhattan Review of Unnatural Acts". Ed. Billy Miller. New York. 1980. n.46 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Straight to Hell: "The Manhattan Review of Unnatural Acts". Ed. Billy Miller. New York. 1980. n.47 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Straight to Hell: "The Manhattan Review of Unnatural Acts". Ed. Billy Miller. New York. n.48, Undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Straight to Hell: "The Manhattan Review of Unnatural Acts". Ed. Billy Miller. New York. n.49, Undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Straight to Hell: "The Manhattan Review of Unnatural Acts". Ed. Billy Miller. New York. n.50, Undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Straight to Hell: "The Manhattan Review of Unnatural Acts". Ed. Billy Miller. New York. n.51, Undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Straight to Hell: "The Manhattan Review of Unnatural Acts". Ed. Billy Miller. New York. n.52, Undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Straight to Hell: "The Manhattan Review of Unnatural Acts". Ed. Billy Miller. New York. n.57, Undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Straight to Hell: "The Manhattan Review of Unnatural Acts". Ed. Billy Miller. New York. n.60, Undated (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Straight to Hell: "The Manhattan Review of Unnatural Acts". Ed. Billy Miller. New York. n.61, Undated (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Straight to Hell: "The Manhattan Review of Unnatural Acts". Ed. Billy Miller. New York. n.62, Undated (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Straight to Hell: "The Manhattan Review of Unnatural Acts". Ed. Billy Miller. New York. n.67, Undated (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Tough Ride. v.1 n.3, Undated (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - TRASH. Australia, D&W Enterprises, 1995. n.132 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, n.74, Undated (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, n.76, Undated (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises. 1994. n.126 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises. 1994. n.127 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises. 1994. n.128 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises. 1994. n.129 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises. 1994. n.130 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises. 1995. n.131 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises. 1995. n.133 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises. 1995. n.134 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 1995. n.135 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 1995. n.136 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 1996. n.137 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 1996. n.138 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 1996. n.139 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 1996. n.140 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 1996. n.141 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 1997. n.142 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 1997. n.143 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 1997. n.144 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 1997. n.145 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 1998. n.146 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 1998. n.147 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 1998. n.148 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 1998. n.149 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 1998. n.150 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 1998. n.151 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 1998. n.152 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 1999. n.153 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2000. n.154 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2000. n.155 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2000. n.156 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2000. n.157 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2000. n.158 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2001. n.159 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2001. n.160 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2001. n.161 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2001. n.162 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2002. n.163 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2002. n.164 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2002. n.165 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2002. n.166 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2002. n.167 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2003. n.168 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2003. n.169 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2003. n.170 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2003. n.171 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2004. n.172 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2004. n.173 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2004. n.175 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2005. n.176 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2005. n.177 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2005. n.178 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2005. n.179 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2005. nos. 180, 182 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2006. n.183 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2006. n.184 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2006. n.185 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2006. n.186 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2006. n.187 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2008. n.188 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2008. n.189 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2008. n.190 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2009. n.191 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2009. n.192 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2009. n.193 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2009. n.194 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Trim Studio Quarterly: "Spartacus". Trim Studio Quarterly, D.C. n.8, Undated (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Vagabond. Portfolio Minnesota, Vagabond Sales. 1964. n.1 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Water Boys. Water Boys, Spring 1997. Issue 6 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Water Boys. Water Boys, Summer 1997. Issue 7 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Water Boys. Water Boys, Spring 1999. Issue 11 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Water Boys.. Water Boys, Summer 1999. Issue 12 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Water Boys. Water Boys, Spring 2000. Issue 13 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Water Boys. Water Boys, Autumn 2001. Issue 14 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Water Boys. Water Boys, Spring 2002. Issue 15 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - When Johnny Comes Marching Home Again. v.1 n.1, Undated (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Wrestling Tales 2. Mr. Xpress, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Zack Magazine. Ed. Rick Castro. v.1 n.1, Undated (Box 15, Folder 35)
- Series IV. Pornographic Film Tie-ins, 1977-1983, undated; 1 Linear Feet in one record carton.
  The tie-ins are arranged alphabetically by publication title.
  This series contains printed materials intended to accompany pornographic films (both film series and individual films); some films can also be found in this collection.
  - Below the Belt. Hardball. California Dream Machine Publishing, Undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Best of Al Parker, Undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - The Bigger the Better, Undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Dangerous, Undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - The Falcon File: Don Talon. California, Falcon Studios. n.3, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - The Falcon File: Against the Rules. California, Falcon Studios. n.8, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Garage Sex. California, DPR Studios, Undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Jockstrap 2. California, Le Salon, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Kept After School. The Nova Starline. n.2, Undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Kinky Selection. Choc, Undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Loaded. Target Studios, Undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Loading Zone, Undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Love, Daddy. Close-up Productions. Feb. 1983. n.1 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - The Main Attraction. The Nova Starline, Undated (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Make My Buddy. A Nova Presentation, Undated (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - ManMeat, Undated (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - A Matter of Size, From the Producers of Huge I & II, Undated (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Mike Arlen's Guys. London, Wetherby Studios. v.6, Undated (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - The Mountain Troopers, Sizzlin' Excerpts from Rangers, Undated (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Nuts and Bolts, Undated (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Ski Summit (Part 1) California, Falcon Studios, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Pit Stop. Surge Studios. Issue 1, Undated (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Probe One: Presenting Scenes from "4 in Hand", Undated (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Solo Suck Off, Undated (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - The Target Stable. New York, Target Studios, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Series V. Catalogs and Calendars, 1997-2006, undated; 1 linear foot in one record carton.
  This series contains erotic calendars; clothing and accessories catalogs; and catalogs and directories for gay pornographic films.
  The materials in this series are arranged alphabetically by title, then chronologically by publication date.
  - Adam Gay Video Directory (7th edition), ed. Doug Lawrence. California, Knight Publishing, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Adam Gay Video Directory (9th edition), ed. Doug Lawrence. California, Knight Publishing, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Black Style. Berlin. [Leather clothing and accessories catalogue], 1996 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Butt Boy 2000: A Gay Pulp Fiction Calendar. California, SOHO Galleries, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Calendario Romano 2005 [Papal Calendar] ed. Piero Pazzi (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Colt Calendar 2003: Hairy Chested Men. California, Colt Studio, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Colt Calendar 2003: Leather Calendar. California, Colt Studio, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Falcon Film/Video Collection. California, Falcon Studios, Undated (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Fireboy. Montreal. 1997-1998 [Underwear catalogue] (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Intermale Amsterdam Catalogue [Europe's international gay bookstore], Undated (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - cuir/latex n.2. France, IEM. [Leather clothing and accessories catalogue], 1998 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Male Nudes Diary. California, Athletic Model Guild. [Contains drawings by Tom of Finland], 1998 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Male Views, Catalog Number Seven, Undated (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Masta [leather video catalog], San Francisco, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Mr. S Leather and Fetters. California. [Leather clothing and accessories catalogue], Undated (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - The 1995 Annual Man Desk Calendar. California, State of Man Publishers (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - The Old Reliable Video Catalogue II. California, Old Reliable Tape Co., 1995 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Project X: International Hard Guide. Paris, PX Presse. [Bar/club guide], 1997 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Rexx. Paris, Rexx. [Leather clothing and accessories catalogue], Undated (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Rim Reader: Membership Listings, vol.3. California, T&T Productions. [Directory], 2001 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - RoB Catalog n.4. California/London/Amsterdam. [Clothing and accessories catalogue], Undated (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Titan Men Calendar 2006, California, TitanMen.com (Box 16, Folder 43)
- Series VI. Advertisements, 1998-2000, undated; 1 linear foot in one record carton.
  This series contains advertisements and mail-orders for pornographic publications and media; newsletters; leaflets; and pamphlets.
  The materials are arranged in alphabetical order by publisher, company, or sender.
  - 3rd World Video. New York, TWV Inc., 1998-2000 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Brown Hanky Journal. New Jersey, D&W Enterprises/Sludgemaster. Texas, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Colt Studios. California, 1998-2000 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Larry Townsend. California, 1998-2000 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous. [Incl. David Forest, MSP Video, Youth Development League], Undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Palm Drive Video. California, Undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Titan Media. California, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - TNT (T&T) Productions. California, Undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Tom of Finland Foundation. California, Undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Series VII. Graphics, 1950-2007, undated; 2 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons.
  This series is divided into two subseries:
  Subseries VII.A. Graphics and Illustrations, 1998-2000, undated
  Subseries VII.B. Japanese publications, 1950-2007, undated
  This series contains artist portfolios, illustrations, and visual ephemera, as well as Japanese Manga and related magazines.
  - Subseries VII.A. Graphics and Illustrations, 1998-2000, undated; 1.25 linear foot in 1 record carton and 1 flat file folder.
    This subseries is in alphabetical order by artist's last name.
    This collection contains artist portfolios, illustrations, miscellaneous visual ephemera, and accompanying documentation.
    - Bastille [photocopies], Undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Bill Ward [photocopies of drawings], Undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - CHAN/Fury161, "Pornotraffic" [magazine and promotional poster; correspondence; portfolio], 1997 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Domino [photocopies of drawings], 1980-1988 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - FUWA and other unidentified artists, drawings/illustrations depicting Japanese Manga characters in various bondage poses and related, 1996, 2000, undated (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Gengoroh Tagame [photocopies of drawings; G's-Men Tagame postcard collection; "biography notes" by Marshall], Undated (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - John Lindell, "After Tom of Finland"; "International" [Two illustrated booklet mock-ups; cover letter from Lindell], 1993 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - John Lindell. "Portholes and Moments 12 (after Tom of Finland)" [Illustrated story. Signed letter from author], 1992 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Julius "Little Dick's Photo Album", Undated (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Lüger. [Two print portfolios of drawings published by Colt Studio], 1992-1993 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous [Pieces on Rex, Harry Bush, and George Quaintance], 1996 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Rip Colt [Untitled drawing by Rip Colt/Jim French], Undated (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Tom of Finland [photocopies of drawings; correspondence], 1991 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Untitled [drawings by unknown artist], Undated (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Subseries VII.B. Japanese Publications, 1950-2007, undated; 2 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons.
    This subseries contains Japanese gay BDSM (bondage, discipline, dominance and submission, sadomasochism) erotic Manga and magazines. Material is in Japanese.
    The Japanese publications are in alphabetical order by author or artist and alphabetically by publication title within.
    - G-Pro Party. G-Project Co. v.1, Undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Gengoroh Tagame. "Emono" and other stories, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Gengoroh Tagame. The House of the Brutes v.1, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Gengoroh Tagame. The House of the Brutes v.2, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Gengoroh Tagame. The House of the Brutes v.3, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Gengoroh Tagame. "Jujitsu Kyoshi" and Other Stories, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Gengoroh Tagame. Naburi-mono, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Gengoroh Tagame. Shirogane-no-Hanna v.1, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Gengoroh Tagame. Shirogane-no-Hanna v.2, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Gengoroh Tagame. Shirogane-no-Hanna v.3, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Goh Mishima. Otoko - The Man, Undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Jinb Gym. "Kaze no yukue" and Other Stories, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Jogg Comics (Raizo Taira). May, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Jogg Comics (Raizo Taira). July, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Kumagoro. Otoko-Dosukoi! v.1, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Kumagoro. Otoko-Dosukoi! v.2, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Masurao - photographed by Yoshito Kazu. G-Project Co, Undated (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Sabu. March 1979. n.49 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Sabu. Aug 1982. n.90 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Sabu. Aug 1985. n.126 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Sabu. April 1989. n.195 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - SM-Z. G-Project. Nov., 1999 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - SM-Z. G-Project. Feb 2000. n.1 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - SM-Z. G-Project. April 2000. n.2 (Box 19, Folder 2a)
    - SM-Z. G-Project. Aug 2000. n.3 (Box 19, Folder 2a)
    - SM-Z. G-Project. March 2001. n.4 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - SM-Z. G-Project. June 2003. n.6 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - SM-Z. G-Project. Aug 2004. n.8 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - SM-Z Super. G-Project. Summer 2006. n.7 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - SM-Z Super. G-Project. Autumn 2006. n.8 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - (Unknown) ?For Youngmen & Guys? May 1975. n.28 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - (Unknown) ?Ho-Man? Sept 2004. n.61 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - (Unknown) October, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - (Unknown) July, 1951 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Series VIII. Web Fiction, 1986-2003, undated; 7 Linear Feet in 7 record cartons.; 3 electronic discs (cd-rom)
  The materials are listed in alphabetical order by title, followed by author name and date.
  This series contains erotic stories originally published via websites, online forums, and email chains. Marshall printed the stories out on paper. A majority of the folders contain complete stories, while a few have been only partially printed out. A selection of the stories were printed on the reverse of Richard Marshall's professional correspondence.
  - 2 x 2, Bawdy Pen, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - A/C Repair, Romaine954, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Abandoned House Raunch, Bkcycler, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - The Accident, Scathole, Undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Adonis Brotherhood (Part 3), Master SIR, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Adult Incest, John Ommestrup, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Adult Incest: Man to Man, Kennyb, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Adult Theater Raunch, Jocksniffer, Undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Adventures on I-10 (Parts 1-3), Dick Hunter, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Adventures on the Road (Part 4), Bearbtmboy, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - After the NCO Club, Happenstance, Undated (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Afternoon Delight, Slick, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Afterwork (Parts 1- 5), Antoms, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Agua Por El Papi Cholo, Tommyhawk1, Undated (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Alex and the Hustler, Joe Wilson, Undated (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - All Dad's Fault, Unknown, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - All In the Family, Maipenraikhap, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Almost Like A Story, Manx952joy, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Always: Daddy's Pup, Unknown, Undated (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Another Hardon Family (Part 1): Hotline Report, Marc Tremaine, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Another One For the Gang, C2cbearhug, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Another Special For the Trash Shack, Bid Red, Undated (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Another Working Day, Billy Boy, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Anthony, The Mover, Unknown, Undated (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Arab Dirt: Dirt Pig Does a Middle Eastern Businessman, Dirt Pig, Undated (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Arabian Adventure, Sam4U, Undated (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Arcade Adventures # 2, Gloryhole Lover, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Armpit Fantasy Comes to Life, sweaty20, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Armpit Slave, Sweaty, Undated (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Army Grunt, Jon H, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - The Army: Code Yellow/Code Brown, Bkcycler, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Army Property, Shulabin, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Arrogance (Parts 1-4), Roderick Shafton, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Art Class, Ozzie Red, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Assistant Jock Sniffer, Ted Tallman, Undated (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Asylum (Parts 2,5,6,7), glaucon55, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - At Their Mercy (Part 13), Dream Spinner, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Auto Serviced, Shaun Dayton, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - The B'anati (Part 1-6), Mickey (Daddy), 1999 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Back Wash Mountain Man, David L. Hass, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Bagging a Bagger, Unknown, Undated (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Bamacop, Cagecashier, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Barbershop Boy (Part 2), Randyboy, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Barn Boy, Dale10, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Baseball Player in the Rest Area; Biting Off a Homer; Proper Submission; Eating Straight Surfer Shit, Unknown, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Baseball Team Rapes Teacher, Conor O'Leary, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Bastille, Unknown, Undated (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Baxter and Joey, Badaug, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Bear Ass Quarterbackin' (Parts 1,2), Michael Dionne, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Bear Cop 2, Bearbtmboys, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Bear in the Woods, BlackBearLover, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Bear's Hairy Dick, Micfriend, Undated (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - Becoming A Real Man (Part 1), Tom Borden, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - Behind the Bar, Unknown, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - Best Fag, Man Loving, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - The Best Stop, Eirewolf, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 56)
  - Big Brother's Bopper- V, Balsam8, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 57)
  - Big Hairy Boss, Story Teller, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 58)
  - Big Jake, Blackmansboy, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 59)
  - Big Luke, Nathan Harvey, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 60)
  - Big Sky Buddy, Sniff42, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 61)
  - Bill and Mike, and Carla; Cuckold and Loving It, Ooz, Undated (Box 20, Folder 62)
  - A BJ for the Plumber, Unknown, Undated (Box 20, Folder 63)
  - Black & White Night, JonH, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 64)
  - Black Daddy's Slut, Michael, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 65)
  - Black Dominance, White Submission, Kevin James, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 66)
  - Black Man's White Pussyboy (Part 1- 2), Percxyz, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 67)
  - Black N White Night, Jon H, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 68)
  - Black Neighbour 3, Unknown, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 69)
  - Black Sperm Engines (Part 2), Braveheart_sm, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 70)
  - Black Stud in the Military, Mark Daniels, Undated (Box 20, Folder 71)
  - Blackstud in the Morning, EbonyLover, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 72)
  - Blues Cock (Parts 1-3), Ron Kelly, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 73)
  - Bob Maloney's Boys, Xwriter, Undated (Box 20, Folder 74)
  - Bonding with Coach, GoJackgo, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 75)
  - The Book Seller, dale10, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 76)
  - Bookstore Lust 2, Grtbttm2, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 77)
  - The Boss's New Sub, Rob D., 2000 (Box 20, Folder 78)
  - The Boy Who Cried Wolf (Part 2), Happenstance, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 79)
  - The Boyfriend: At Joey's House, Dale10, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 80)
  - Boys "Do" Men, BALSAM8, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 81)
  - The Boys In the Band, Unknown, Undated (Box 20, Folder 82)
  - Brawn, Mark, Undated (Box 20, Folder 83)
  - Bringing Lenny Along, Roderick Shafton, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 84)
  - Broken Jock (Part 1- 5), Alan, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 85)
  - Brother Lust (Part 4), Rim4You, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 86)
  - Brother Raunch, Mark Kelly, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 87)
  - Brother's First Time, D, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 88)
  - Brown Hanky, Rim4you, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 89)
  - Builder, Andy McDonald, Undated (Box 20, Folder 90)
  - Bull Daddies (Part 4), WorshipsMusclesChubs, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 91)
  - Bull Session, Roderick Shafton, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 92)
  - Burglars! Burglars!, Roderick Shafton, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 93)
  - Bus Rider, Water Closet Clark, Undated (Box 20, Folder 94)
  - Bus Station Hijinks #3, Cgard43, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 95)
  - Business Trip Abroad, Paul Richarson, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 96)
  - Butch, Charlie Brown, and Snoopy 2, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 97)